saleshacker.com 2019-04-05

# Privacy Policy | Sales Hacker

### **Last Edited: May 24, 2018  
**

At Sales Hacker, we appreciate your use of and contributions to our website, our conference websites, our mobile conference apps, our content, and ultimately our greater digital community.

Sales Hacker takes your privacy very seriously and is committed to protecting your personal information.

We encourage you to read this privacy policy to understand the information we collect and how we use and disclose it. This policy applies to all of our online properties, including but not limited to conferences, special intimate events, and more.

This privacy policy has been uniquely compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. 

PII, as used in U.S. privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. 

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

## **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website, conference pages and mobile apps?**

### 1) Information that you provide

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter the following information and details to help you with your experience:

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Job title
  * Company

This may occur, for example, when you register for a webinar, or download an eBook from our website. Specifically, this happens when you explicitly complete a form on our website to access any type of content.

### 2) Cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technology

We use various technologies to collect information automatically when you access our web properties and consume our content – this is including but not limited to cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.

Cookies are bits of electronic information that can be transferred to your computer or other electronic device to uniquely identify your browser.

When you access our content, we may place one or more cookies on your computer or other electronic device or use other technologies that provide similar functionality.

The use of cookies helps us improve the quality and relevance of content displayed to you, by identifying information which is most interesting to you, and helps us measure the effectiveness of our advertising.

At any time, you may adjust settings on your browser to refuse cookies according to the instructions related to your browser.

You may also choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Chrome) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies, some features will be disabled, and your site experience is likely to be less efficient as some of our services may not function properly.

### 3) Country data based on your IP

If you register for a webinar or download an eBook, for example, we may collect the location of your device based on your IP address. This helps us delineate where you located in the world, and based on that, we will follow each country’s data compliance regulations to their fullest effect.

## **How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

**1)** To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

**2)** To send periodic emails regarding other offers, products and/or services.

**3)** To send you event related updates, reminders and confirmations.

**4)** To send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages.

**5)** To respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service and support.

**6)** To communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards and events offered by Sales Hacker and our partners, as well as provide news and information we think will be of interest to you.

**7)** Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our content and website performance.

**8)** To personalize content and present you with advertising, content or features that we believe will be of interest or useful to you.

**9)** Facilitate contests, sweepstakes and promotions and process and deliver entries and rewards. An example of this might be our Sales Hacker Top 50 Awards.

### **Email Management**

You may receive email from Sales Hacker for a variety of reasons – for example, if you took an action through our website, you signed up for specialty content, or perhaps you registered for an event or conference.

All Sales Hacker emails will include a link in the footer, where you can select your communication preferences or unsubscribe altogether.

Also, you can manage your receipt of some types of communication by following the instructions included in the email we send you.

Please note that, even if you unsubscribe from certain email correspondences, we may still need to email you in the event there is an important transactional or administrative issue we need to resolve with you. An example of this might be processing a refund for an event ticket that you can no longer attend.

## **When do we share and disclose your information?**

Your privacy is extremely important to us and we are committed to protecting your information that identifies you personally. We will only share personal information that you provide us under the following circumstances:

### **1) With your consent**

When you explicitly consent or allow Sales Hacker to share your personal information. This happens when you submit your information through many of our content offers, events or services.

For example, if you choose to sign up for an exclusive piece of premium content via a form – your name, phone number, email address, job title, and company will be collected by Sales Hacker.

### **2) Service providers to Sales Hacker**

When Sales Hacker hires a service provider to help operate the Services or our business, we may give access to personal information only as appropriate to perform the service for Sales Hacker, and subject to the terms of this privacy policy.

### **3) Partners with whom we conduct business**

When Sales Hacker partners up with other businesses to offer products and services, we may share information with those business partners only as needed to provide those products and services and only subject to the terms of this privacy policy.

### **4) Legal obligation or protection from harm**

When Sales Hacker has a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any requirement of law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce or investigate a potential violation of the Terms of Use, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise respond to fraud, security or technical concerns, (d) support auditing and compliance functions, or (e) protect the rights, property, or safety of Sales Hacker, its users, or the public against harm.

### **5) Business transfers**

If and when Sales Hacker is involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of transfer or sale of some or all of its business, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, we may share your personal information in connection with that transaction.

## **How do we protect visitor information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security breaches and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We use regular Malware Scanning, as well as an SSL certificate.

### **Third Party Disclosure**

When you register for a sponsored event, your information may be shared with our event partners. You may opt out of communications at any time.

### **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### **Google**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**We have implemented the following:**

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

### **Opting out:**

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

### **How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

### **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

### **Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

  * Within 1 Business Day we will notify the users via email and site notifications:  

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

### **CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

### **We collect your email address in order to:**

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred

### **To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM we agree to the following:**

  * NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

### **Contacting Us**

If you have questions regarding this privacy policy or about Sales Hacker’s privacy practices, you may **[contact us](https://www.saleshacker.com/contact/)** using the information below.

Sales Hacker Inc.

PO Box 503

Armonk, NY 10504

U.S.A.

Request access to your personal data here: [Privacy Request Form](http://preferences.saleshacker.com/privacy_requests)

Regarding other privacy-related matters, email us at [privacy@saleshacker.com](mailto:privacy@saleshacker.com)
